explore huh come here
what
what what is
that what the [__] that was not there
last night no that was [__] wasn't there
last night we pulled up here I come over
here and set up this solo thing last
night you ain't you ain't do
that holy [__]
hi um so I kind of have something crazy
and weren't sure who to call so we were
camping off of the Forest Road right
next to uh Douglas fur last night there
was a rock that we woke up to that was
carved into that said I will kill
again um placed next to our van on a
tree stump um okay but I didn't know
felt like we should have called and told
somebody there was a note that said I
will kill again scrawled on a rock and
left near a van in the middle of the
night
yeah okay yeah okay all right so what we
need to do um did you take a photo of it
at all yes and a video so what we want
to do um we we need to contact um I'm
going to have you contact the W County
Sheriff's Office okay and they're the
ones that take care of that for us here
but it's good for us to know as well uh
well let's see
what is
it feeling really secure right
now James Griffin okay is a for service
Patrol Captain and then he can pass it
on with uh the wcom p uh W County for
the sheriff's office as well I will give
him a call all right thank you for
letting us know thank
you
careful Alex how secure do you feel up
here now you don't even
know this isn't even the cop's number
this is a forest service
guy hi um so I had kind of have a a
weird thing I just spoke with the
glacier uh Public Service Center and
they recommended we call you guys um we
were camped last night right next to the
Douglas fur Campground off of that
Forest Road woke up this morning and
there was a Rock placed next to the van
and scrawled into the Rock laid on top
of this tree stump was I will kill again
probably just a goofy kid thing but
figured we should probably report it
okay anything K are not worried it's
actually genuine threat um well honestly
I think that's just what I'm trying to
convince myself of are you having
problems with anybody no no ma'am here's
the thing we camped in the middle of the
forest maybe a mile and a half off the
main road ain't no ain't no happen
stance that somebody just stumbles upon
you it's so dark up here at night you
can't see your hand in front of your
face it it's just
Eerie
[Music]
okay ifn itead and okay all righty
thanks
byebye man we did our part you know
there was it we're at Cloud n right now
or no uh Chair 9 it's a pizza right down
the
road uh no we left it right there we did
take pictures of it but like I said it's
it's right down the road we left it
right where it was just so we could get
into service and and Away get the hell
away from the rock let me are you going
to be atair for a few minutes yeah we'll
be here let me call my sergeant um and
see if he wants me to collect the rock
or if just sufficient so if y'all don't
want the Rock I'm going to go back and
get it that's pretty cool like I've
never been left a love note from a
serial killer
it's I guess you know one of my thoughts
is you know have we had anything
suspicious like that happen in that area
were um let me ask my sergeant what he
dig and then I'll call you back ma' and
I don't know if it counts anything on
the police scale but I'm a pretty wild
individual and not easily scared and she
gave me the heie
jibbies no that would that would weird
any normal person out yeah and I'm not
normal that's the thing I'm very
abnormal but that [__] scared me and the
unnormal people yeah how long do you
think before you call back so once we go
inside the service kind of dips out less
than five minutes okay perfect I'll just
stay out here yeah okay I'll just make a
call and call you back thank you all
right thanks byebye that was the best
one yet that lady actually cared you
I'll just make a call and call you back
thank you all right than
byebye that was the best one yet that
lady actually cared you look so creeped
out
woman
yeah hey to all the people who think
this is fake I don't I not concerned
that we're going to die but just the
it's out in the middle of [__]
nowhere like do you honestly feel that a
murderous individual put that
there
yeah I mean I'll be honest I don't know
got to pit him my tummy kind of to all
the people who think this is fake what
you tell
them nah like I want to
puke I called I called the authorities
yeah if if we're on the phone with
goddamn the government that means some
[__] has
happened all right I don't like it boy
I'm going to go have a [__]
beer beated as the person who made the
call I guess okay so I need to enter
your inform do you need like my blood
type
or dental records are they coming out
here okay got to send them pictures yeah
yeah up
whatever awesome all
righty and we have the is there a name
to the campground that you're at um it
wasn't a campground for service road
forest service road right past Douglas
fur Campground right Doug Camp uh 31
also Canyon Creek Road Forest Service
Road number 31 yep and you said on the
north side of the road yes ma'am it's
the if you drive up that road it's the
very first sight on the left if they
ever drive up there and look you'll be
like yeah ain't no way somebody just
stumbled up on there is creepy
boy yeah and there's a little babblin
look right below it and you know it'
muffle the sound to anybody's footsteps
if you're in that van well be careful
hey ma'am don't don't worry if somebody
tries to serial kill us we're going to
try and serial kill him all right it's
fair fair
game well you know I mean maybe like
leave a photo of your your teeth
Impressions or something yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah all
right you from here hold on he's from
here come here he's from here come here
dude hey we are camped out right up here
on that forest service road right where
part of southy from huh where part of
the southy from what makes you think I'm
from the south I'm from South I'm from
Georgia go dogs baby and so we are
camped out there right and we stayed
there two of the last three nights and
we wake up and on show look at it this
is what we
find oh that's can you see that yeah I
see
yeah uh what what road was that on
specifically right up here you know
right right up there the same side by uh
by uh what is it Horseshoe Bend yeah on
the other side so that little forest
service road on the same side you know
right there by the the campground with
you no nobody no nobody does any of that
stuff without my
authorization we got the right guy all
right God damn dude ain't many people
can clean up after that [__] um yeah
that's uh I'm going to have to talk to
some people about that cuz I don't
approve admittedly sometimes we don't
like turists but like that's that's just
an act of deterrent and that's an act of
deterrent on all of our income I'm used
to doing dirt uh because I didn't
authorize it then hey they're they're
[__] freelance and I don't approve
that [__] you have to talk [__] if you
can just do it D what's your name dude z
z Joe nice to meet you good to meet you
sir decided that since the police do not
need the Stone from the serial killer
what are we going to do we're going to
go get it uh just so everyone knows how
remote our campsite was this is where
you turn off it's the left right after
the dougas fur Campground right after
the nookat river here in the mount
Beaker snowwy National
Forest this it what if there's somebody
there we're getting that guy give me my
goddamn Rock what you talking about I'm
going to be like hey I left my Rock I
got to come get it hey I left my Rock
what the hell yeah yeah you going to
argue with me if I say I come get my
rock that says I will kill again hey
this is it right here this is
it oh [__] why do we even Bull in here I
don't
know f
man there's a truck
there [__] let's go down
him
[__] [__] somebody staying here I it is
let's go talk to him
hello hey guys we just wanted to uh warn
you about something we stayed here last
night were you asleep
sleep oh where you at sorry hey we
stayed here last night I'm going to show
you something real quick so you see this
right here yeah we stayed here last
night and we reported this this was not
here when we went to bed but this rock
right here that somebody scrolled I will
kill again was laid on this stump
sometime between when we went to bed and
when we came back and we came back to
get the rock because it freaked us the
[__] out dude you guys come back we were
here last night in the morning and it
was there so we left it there and went
down and got service and called the cops
we came back to get this and we saw you
here we're like Hey we're going to tell
you what we found we stayed here two out
of the last three nights it's completely
silent the [__] Brook is wonderful
but that was really freaky dude yeah I
mean I'm strapped so yeah I said hey if
you're going to come see kill me yeah
God damn fair game cuz exactly
hey thanks for the warning yeah I'm c c
my name is Joe man are you staying up
here in the P up Joe Joe that's out
might just stay up and wait for this
dude think maybe it's just like a local
spot and the locals wanted us out and
that's what it I'm going to take my
Hatchet put it in yep hey [__] her in
and find out hey man thank you here from
me something happened to me all right we
know be safe cool nice to meet you dude
we got it oh man
we have a
Talisman what if he put a GPS tracker on
our [__]
van what if it's in the Rock what if you
knew we'd take the
rock hey Alex I love van life don't you
like what the [__] why did we do
this you ever thought about that
like like bro you got a good life why
did you go get the zero killer Rock from
the creepy
campsite we had no option did we uh-uh
uhuh I saw no other option yeah YOLO
here killer Rock not sure why we did it
but here we are